A Guide to the Kathleen Booth Williams Papers, 1860-ca. 1982
Library of Virginia
- Kathleen Booth Williams Papers, 1860-ca. 1982. (Box 1-13)
  - Genealogical Notes: Leigh-Watkins Families (Box 8, Folder 361)
  - Genealogical Notes: Leitch Family (Box 8, Folder 362)
  - Genealogical Notes: Lincoln Family (Box 8, Folder 363)
  - Genealogical Notes: Lipscomb Family (Box 8, Folder 364)
  - Genealogical Notes: Lowry Family (Box 8, Folder 365)
  - Genealogical Notes: Mahon Family (Box 8, Folder 366)
  - Genealogical Notes: Major Family (Box 8, Folder 367)
  - Genealogical Notes: Malone-Barrow Families (Box 8, Folder 368)
  - Genealogical Notes: Marks Family (Box 8, Folder 369)
  - Genealogical Notes: Marshall Family (Box 8, Folder 370)
  - Genealogical Notes: Massie-Bullock Family (Box 8, Folder 371)
  - Genealogical Notes: Matlock Family (Box 8, Folder 372)
  - Genealogical Notes: Mattox/Maddox Family (Box 8, Folder 373)
  - Genealogical Notes: McCubbin Family (Box 8, Folder 374)
  - Genealogical Notes: McGehee Family (Box 8, Folder 375)
  - Genealogical Notes: MacGregor Family (Box 8, Folder 376)
  - Genealogical Notes: Meador(s)-Meadow Families (Box 8, Folder 377)
  - Genealogical Notes: Merriman Family (Box 8, Folder 378)
  - Genealogical Notes: Mills Family (Box 8, Folder 379)
  - Genealogical Notes: Mohorn Family (Box 8, Folder 380)
  - Genealogical Notes: Montague Family (Box 8, Folder 381)
  - Genealogical Notes: Moore Family (Box 8, Folder 382)
  - Genealogical Notes: Moorman Family (Box 8, Folder 383)
  - Genealogical Notes: Morgan Family (Box 8, Folder 384)
  - Genealogical Notes: Moseley Family (Box 8, Folder 385)
  - Genealogical Notes: Nowlin Family (Box 8, Folder 386)
  - Genealogical Notes: Owen Family (Box 8, Folder 387)
  - Genealogical Notes: Pace Family (Box 8, Folder 388)
  - Genealogical Notes: Parham Family (Box 8, Folder 389)
  - Genealogical Notes: Parrish Family (Box 8, Folder 390)
  - Genealogical Notes: Pearson Family (Box 8, Folder 391)
  - Genealogical Notes: Peed Family (Box 8, Folder 392)
  - Genealogical Notes: Pendleton Family (Box 8, Folder 393)
  - Genealogical Notes: Penn Family (Box 8, Folder 394)
  - Genealogical Notes: Pennell Family (Box 8, Folder 395)
  - Genealogical Notes: Perdue Family (Box 8, Folder 396)
  - Genealogical Notes: Perkins Family (Box 8, Folder 397)
  - Genealogical Notes: Pettus Family (Box 8, Folder 398)
  - Genealogical Notes: Phifer Family (Box 8, Folder 399)
  - Genealogical Notes: Phillips Family (Box 8, Folder 400)
  - Genealogical Notes: Pierce Family (Box 8, Folder 401)
  - Genealogical Notes: Piggott Family (Box 8, Folder 402)
  - Genealogical Notes: Poindexter Family (Box 8, Folder 403)
  - Genealogical Notes: Pollard Family (Box 8, Folder 404)
  - Genealogical Notes: Powell-Booth Families (Box 8, Folder 405)
  - Genealogical Notes: Powell-Tuggle Families (Box 8, Folder 406)
  - Genealogical Notes: Price Family (Box 8, Folder 407)
  - Genealogical Notes: Pritchett Family (Box 8, Folder 408)
  - Genealogical Notes: Pugh Family (Box 8, Folder 409)
  - Genealogical Notes: Ragland Family (Box 8, Folder 410)
  - Genealogical Notes: Raines Family (Box 8, Folder 411)
  - Genealogical Notes: Ramsey Family (Box 8, Folder 412)
  - Genealogical Notes: Rash Family (Box 8, Folder 413)
  - Genealogical Notes: Redding Family (Box 8, Folder 414)
  - Genealogical Notes: Rees Family (Box 8, Folder 415)
  - Genealogical Notes: Reese Family (Box 8, Folder 416)
  - Genealogical Notes: Reeves Family (Box 8, Folder 417)
  - Genealogical Notes: Reynolds Family (Box 8, Folder 418)
  - Genealogical Notes: Richardson Family (Box 8, Folder 419)
  - Genealogical Notes: Rives Family (Box 8, Folder 420)
  - Genealogical Notes: Robbins Family (Box 8, Folder 421)
  - Genealogical Notes: Robertson Family (Box 8, Folder 422)
  - Genealogical Notes: Robinson/Robertson Families (Box 8, Folder 423)
  - Genealogical Notes: Rogers Family (Box 8, Folder 424)
  - Genealogical Notes: Roper Family (Box 8, Folder 425)
  - Genealogical Notes: Routon Family (Box 8, Folder 426)
  - Genealogical Notes: Russell Family (Box 8, Folder 427)
  - Genealogical Notes: Russell-Haymes Family (Box 8, Folder 428)
  - Genealogical Notes: Ryerson Family (Box 8, Folder 429)
  - Genealogical Notes: Sample Family (Box 8, Folder 430)
  - Genealogical Notes: Saunders Family (Box 8, Folder 431)
  - Genealogical Notes: Saunders-Penick Families (Box 8, Folder 432)
  - Genealogical Notes: Savedge Family (Box 8, Folder 433)
  - Genealogical Notes: Scearce Family (Box 8, Folder 434)
  - Genealogical Notes: Semple Family (Box 8, Folder 435)
  - Genealogical Notes: Shelburn(e) Family (Box 8, Folder 436)
  - Genealogical Notes: Shelton Family (Box 8, Folder 437)
  - Genealogical Notes: Sinclair Family (Box 8, Folder 438)
  - Genealogical Notes: Slayton Family (Box 8, Folder 439)
  - Genealogical Notes: Smith Family (Box 8, Folder 440)
  - Genealogical Notes: Stamps Family (Box 8, Folder 441)
  - Genealogical Notes: (John) Stamps Family (Box 8, Folder 442)
  - Genealogical Notes: Steger Family (Box 8, Folder 443)
  - Genealogical Notes: Stokes Family (Box 8, Folder 444)
  - Genealogical Notes: Street Family (Box 8, Folder 445)
  - Genealogical Notes: Tabb Family (Box 9, Folder 446)
  - Genealogical Notes: Tate Family (Box 9, Folder 447)
  - Genealogical Notes: Taylor Family (Box 9, Folder 448)
  - Genealogical Notes: Templeton Family (Box 9, Folder 449)
  - Genealogical Notes: Terry Family (Box 9, Folder 450)
  - Genealogical Notes: Thacker Family (Box 9, Folder 451)
  - Genealogical Notes: Thompson Family (Box 9, Folder 452)
  - Genealogical Notes: Thornton Family (Box 9, Folder 453)
  - Genealogical Notes: Thurston Family (Box 9, Folder 454)
  - Genealogical Notes: Tompkins Family (Box 9, Folder 455)
  - Genealogical Notes: Tunstall Family (Box 9, Folder 457-458)
  - Genealogical Notes: Turley Family (Box 9, Folder 459)
  - Genealogical Notes: Turnbull Family (Box 9, Folder 460)
  - Genealogical Notes: Updike Family (Box 9, Folder 461)
  - Genealogical Notes: Vaden Family (Box 9, Folder 462)
  - Genealogical Notes: Vaughan Family (Box 9, Folder 463)
  - Genealogical Notes: Walker Family (Box 9, Folder 464)
  - Genealogical Notes: Wall Family (Box 9, Folder 465)
  - Genealogical Notes: Waller Family (Box 9, Folder 466)
  - Genealogical Notes: Walthall Family (Box 9, Folder 467)
  - Genealogical Notes: Walters Family (Box 9, Folder 468)
  - Genealogical Notes: Walton Family (Box 9, Folder 469)
  - Genealogical Notes: Ward Family (Box 9, Folder 470)
  - Genealogical Notes: Warren Family (Box 9, Folder 471)
  - Genealogical Notes: Watkins Family (Box 9, Folder 472)
  - Genealogical Notes: Welborn Family (Box 9, Folder 473)
  - Genealogical Notes: White Family (Box 9, Folder 474)
  - Genealogical Notes: Whitehead Family (Box 9, Folder 475)
  - Genealogical Notes: Wilkinson Family (Box 9, Folder 476)
  - Genealogical Notes: Williams Family (Box 9, Folder 477-478)
  - Genealogical Notes: Willis Family (Box 9, Folder 479)
  - Genealogical Notes: Wilson Family (Box 9, Folder 480)
  - Genealogical Notes: Witcher Family (Box 9, Folder 481)
  - Genealogical Notes: Withers Family (Box 9, Folder 482)
  - Genealogical Notes: Wood Family (Box 9, Folder 483)
  - Genealogical Notes: Wood-Harvey Family (Box 9, Folder 484)
  - Genealogical Notes: Wooding Family (Box 9, Folder 485-488)
  - Genealogical Notes: Wooding-Hill Families (Box 9, Folder 489)
  - Genealogical Notes: Worsham Family (Box 9, Folder 490)
  - Genealogical Notes: Wyatt Family (Box 9, Folder 491)
  - Genealogical Notes: Yancey Family (Box 9, Folder 492)
  - Genealogical Notes: Yates Family (Box 9, Folder 493)
  - Genealogical Notes: Yeargin Family (Box 9, Folder 494)
  - Genealogical Notes: Yeatts Family (Box 9, Folder 495)
  - Genealogical Notes: Young Family (Box 9, Folder 496)
  - Miscellaneous Genealogical Notes: Adams-Barnes-Batchelder-Baynham-Booker-Bourne-Calloway Families (Box 9, Folder 497)
  - Miscellaneous Genealogical Notes: Page-Jones-Ramey-Keen-Napier-Witcher-Chiles-Moorman-Dillard Families (Box 9, Folder 498)
  - Miscellaneous Genealogical Notes: Taylor-Waller-West-Gregory-Carter-Skipwith-Littlepage Families (Box 9, Folder 499)
  - Miscelleanous Genealogical Notes (Box 9, Folder 500-503)
  - County Record Abstracts: Amelia County--Wills (Box 10, Folder 504)
  - County Record Abstracts: Amelia County--Surveys, 1781-1802 (Box 10, Folder 505)
  - County Record Abstracts: Charlotte County--Insolvents, 1787 (Box 10, Folder 506)
  - County Record Abstracts: Culpeper County--Wills (Box 10, Folder 507)
  - County Record Abstracts: Dinwiddie County--Surveyor's Plat Book (Box 10, Folder 508)
  - County Record Abstracts: Halifax County--Deed Book No. 1 (Box 10, Folder 509)
  - County Record Abstracts: Halifax County--Deed Book No. 1, part 2 (Box 10, Folder 510-511)
  - County Record Abstracts: Halifax County-Deed Book No. 2 (Box 10, Folder 512)
  - County Record Abstracts: Halifax County--Wills (Box 10, Folder 513)
  - County Record Abstracts: Halifax County--Wills, Index and Abstracts (Box 10, Folder 514)
  - County Record Abstracts: Henrico County--Will Book, 1781-89, Index (Box 10, Folder 515)
  - County Record Abstracts: Lunenburg County--Tax List, 1783 (Box 10, Folder 516)
  - County Record Abstracts: Pittsylvania County--Deeds (Box 10, Folder 517)
  - County Record Abstracts: Pittsylvania County--Wills, 1800-70, Index (Box 10, Folder 518-519)
  - County Record Abstracts: Pittsylvania County--List of Surveys, 1779 (Box 10, Folder 520)
  - County Record Abstracts: Prince George County--Deeds (Box 10, Folder 521)
  - County Record Abstracts: Danville City--Deeds and Wills (Box 10, Folder 522)
  - County Record Abstracts: Orange, Edgecombe, Surry Counties, NC (Box 10, Folder 523)
  - Marriage Abstracts: Caroline County, 1795, 1803 (Box 10, Folder 524)
  - Marriage Abstracts: Cumberland County (Box 10, Folder 525)
  - Marriage Abstracts: Fauquier County (Box 10, Folder 526)
  - Marriage Abstracts: Fauquier County, Index (Box 10, Folder 527)
  - Marriage Abstracts: Franklin County, 1756-1858, Bride Index (Box 10, Folder 528)
  - Marriage Abstracts: Halifax County (Box 10, Folder 529)
  - Marriage Abstracts: Halifax County, 1753-1854 (A-R) (Box 10, Folder 530)
  - Marriage Abstracts: Halifax County, 1753-1854 (S-Y) (Box 10, Folder 531)
  - Marriage Abstracts: Henry County (Box 10, Folder 532)
  - Marriage Abstracts: Mecklenburg County, 1765-1810 (Box 10, Folder 533)
  - Marriage Abstracts: Pittsylvania County, ca. 1770-1832 (Box 10, Folder 534)
  - Marriage Abstracts: Pittsylvania County (Box 10, Folder 535)
  - Marriage Abstracts: Pittsylvania County, ca. 1811-1836 (Box 10, Folder 536)
  - Marriage Abstracts: Shenandoah County (Box 10, Folder 537)
  - Marriage Abstracts: Westmoreland County, Inferred (Box 10, Folder 538)
  - Marriage Abstracts: Caswell County, NC (Box 10, Folder 539)
  - Marriage Abstracts: From Pensioners, Vol. 18 (Box 10, Folder 540)
  - Marriage Abstracts: Miscellaneous Counties (Box 10, Folder 541)
  - Cemetery Inscriptions (Box 11, Folder 542)
  - Cemetery Inscriptions: Alexandria, Presbyterian Cemetery (Box 11, Folder 543)
  - Cemetery Inscriptions: Alexandria, St. Paul's Episcopal (Box 11, Folder 544)
  - Census Abstracts (Box 11, Folder 545-547)
  - Census, Tax List, Tithable Abstracts (Box 11, Folder 548)
  - Church Records: Abingdon Parish, Gloucester County (Box 11, Folder 549)
  - Church Records: Antrim Parish Vestry Book, Abstracts (Box 11, Folder 550)
  - Church Records: Cumberland Parish (includes Rev. John Cameron's Reg.) (Box 11, Folder 551)
  - Church Records: Quaker Record Abstracts (Box 11, Folder 552)
  - Church Records: Sandy Creek Baptist Church, Minutes, 1824-1880 (Box 11, Folder 553)
  - Church Records: York Co. Methodist Church Minutes (Box 11, Folder 554)
  - Military Records: Brunswick Co., Militia, 1758 (Box 11, Folder 555)
  - Military Records: Halifax Co., Revolutionary Soldiers (Box 11, Folder 556)
  - Military Records: King & Queen Co., Public Service Claims (Box 11, Folder 557)
  - Military Records: Lunenburg Co., Revolutionary Soldiers (Box 11, Folder 558)
  - Military Records: Pittsylvania Co., Oaths of Allegiance, 1777 (Box 11, Folder 559)
  - Military Records: Pittsylvania Co., Public Service Claims (index) (Box 11, Folder 560)
  - Military Records: Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 561)
  - Military Records: Revolutionary War Pension--William COLE (Box 11, Folder 562)
  - Military Records: Revolutionary War Pension--John GATES (Box 11, Folder 563)
  - Miliary Records: Revolutionary War Pension--Christopher KERBY (Box 11, Folder 564)
  - Military Records: Revolutionary War Pension: William KERBY (Box 11, Folder 565)
  - Military Records: Revolutionary War Pension: William NELSON (Box 11, Folder 566)
  - Military Records: Revolutionary War Pension: James WALDREPE (Box 11, Folder 567)
  - Military Records: Revolutionary War Soldiers buried in Delaware Co., Ohio (Box 11, Folder 568)
  - Military Records: Revolutionary War Soldiers buried in Texas (Box 11, Folder 569)
  - Military Records: Society of the Cincinnati, List of Original Members (Box 11, Folder 570)
  - Military Records: Virginia Women of the Revolution, 1774-1784 (Box 11, Folder 571)
  - Military Records: Confederate Soldiers, Pitt Co., NC (Box 11, Folder 572)
  - Military Records: Civil War Reminiscences (Box 11, Folder 573)
  - Newspaper Abstracts: Charlotte Gazette Queries (Box 11, Folder 574)
  - Newspaper Abstracts: The Daily Press Queries (Box 11, Folder 575)
  - Newspaper Abstracts: The Franklin News-Post (Box 11, Folder 576)
  - Newspaper Abstracts: The Journal (Box 11, Folder 577)
  - Newspaper Abstracts: Kenbridge-Victoria Dispatch Queries (Box 11, Folder 578)
  - Newspaper Abstracts: The Shreveport Journal Queries (Box 11, Folder 579)
  - Newspaper Abstracts: The Virginia Gazette Queries (Box 11, Folder 580)
  - Subject Files: Index to Wood's History of Albemarle Co. (Box 11, Folder 581)
  - Subject Files: Amelia County (Box 11, Folder 582)
  - Subject Files: Bristol to America (Box 11, Folder 583)
  - Subject Files: British Mercantile Claims (Box 11, Folder 584)
  - Subject Files: Danville City Directory, Abstracts, 1917 (Box 11, Folder 585)
  - Subject Files: Goochland County (Box 11, Folder 586)
  - Subject Files: Hale's Ford Academy (Box 11, Folder 587)
  - Subject Files: Isle of Wight County (Box 11, Folder 588)
  - Subject Files: Nottoway County Homes (Box 11, Folder 589)
  - Subject Files: Nottoway County Homes, part 2 (Box 11, Folder 590)
  - Printed Materials: The Cotter's Saturday Night, Robert Burns (Box 12, Folder 591)
  - Printed Materials: Florida Genealogical Journal, Vol. 6, No. 2 (Box 12, Folder 592)
  - Printed Materials: Four States Genealogist, Vol. 1, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 593)
  - Printed Materials: Four States Genealogist, Vol. 2, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 594)
  - Printed Materials: Henry County, Tennessee Old Time Stuff, E. Whitley (Box 12, Folder 595)
  - Printed Materials: A Hornbook of Virginia History (Box 12, Folder 596)
  - Printed Materials: Marriages of Pittsylvania County, 1767-1805, C. L. Knorr (Box 12, Folder 597)
  - Printed Materials: My Dear Jane, M. J. Kennard (Box 12, Folder 598)
  - Autobiography of A. K. Booth (Box 12, Folder 599)
  - Material from the Green Scrapbook (Box 12, Folder 600)
  - Scrapbook of Lula D. Moir (Box 12, Folder 601)
  - Scrapbook (Daddy's families with a few items not placed) (Box 12, Folder 602-604)
  - Ephemera (Box 12, Folder 605)
  - Photographs: Identified (Box 13, Folder 606-607)
  - Photographs: Unidentified (Box 13, Folder 608-609)
  - Drawings (Box 13, Folder 610)
  - Index Card Files: Marriages, DR-Z (Box 1-12)
  - Index Card Files: Marriages of Some Virginia Families, 1607-1800 (A-H) by Dorothy Wulfeck (Box 13-15)
  - Index Card Files: Marriages from DAR Magazine, A-Z (Box 15)
  - Index Card Files: Genealogical Abstracts from Revolutionary Pensions, A-B (Box 16)
  - Index Card Files: Cumberland County Marriages, ca. 1750-1840, A-Z (Box 17-18)
  - Index Card Files: Augusta County Marriages, 1748-1773, A-Y (Box 18)
  - Index Card Files: Amherst County Marriages, ca. 1773-1853, A-W (Box 18)
  - Index Card Files: Frederick County Marriages, 1788-1791, A-Z (Box 19-20)
  - Index Card Files: Index to Clients/Correspondents (Box 21)
  - Index Card Files: List of Published Genealogical Works (Box 21)
  - Index Card Files: Amherst in the Revolution Genealogical Abstracts (Box 21)
  - Index Card Files: Middlesex County Will Book A (Box 21)
  - Index Card Files: Bedford County Wills Book 1 (Box 21)
  - Index Card Files: Goochland County Wills, A-W (Box 21)
  - Index Card Files: Pittsylvania County Will Abstracts Deed and Will Book 11, A-Y (Box 22)
  - Index Card Files: Index to Marriages in Old Homes and Families of Nottoway County (Box 22)
  - Index Card Files: Marriages from the Douglas Register, A-W (Box 22)
  - Index Card Files: Kanawha County, W. Va. Marriages, 1814-1850 (Box 22)
  - Index Card Files: Monogalia County Marriages, 1794-1812 (Box 23)
  - Index Card Files: Patrick County Marriages, 1785-1796 (Box 23)
  - Index Card Files: Pittsylvania County Marriages from Robertson Book, A-Y (Box 23)
  - Index Card Files: Craven County, N.C. Marriages, ca. 1783-1860 (Box 23)
  - Index Card Files: Grayson County Marriages, 1801-1818, n.d. (Box 23)
  - Index Card Files: Miscellaneous Card File (Box 23)